Reza Dwi Andrianto

Born in Cilacap, 27 September 2001 | +6281391686770 | rezadwiandrianto@gmail.com | linkedin.com/rezada | github.com/rezamiaw | behance.net/rezamiaw | Bandung, West Java

Summary

Recent graduate with a Bachelor's degree in Informatics, with 4 months of experience as a front-end developer. Experienced in mobile and web application development, using programming languages such as HTML5, CSS, ReactJS, NextJS, and Flutter. My education has provided me with a strong understanding of technology

Work Experience

Frontend Developer Intern · Gikslab Indonesia July 2023 — Sept 2023

- Developing a company dashboard using ReactJS, including adding notification settings, revamping the Task Detail design, improving Task Detail functionality, making the Kanban board responsive, and implementing the Task popup function
- Developing a company profile website using NextJS, including adding a responsive design to the homepage.

Researcher Intern · PT Telkom Indonesia (Persero) Dec 2019 — May 2019

- Creating an automated script (bot) using UiPath
- Exploring RPA (Robotic Process Automation) materials

Organizational Experience

Logistics Chair · Telkom Edutainment Aug 2021 — Feb 2022

- Directing staff to procure facility needs
- Providing live streaming on YouTube
- Finding the right vendor to implement webinars

Education

Telkom University

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering GPA 3.54/4.00 Aug 2020 — Aug 2024

• Successfully developed a learning prototype called 'Aksun'. It is an innovative platform that makes it easy for users to learn to read the Sundanese script

Certificates & Training

Intellectual Property Rights (AKSUN Learning Application) · Kemenkumham RI 2024

Frontend – Intern · Gikslab Internship Program 2023

- Developing a company dashboard tool using ReactJS
- Developing a company profile website using NextJS

Frontend - React · My Skill 2023

- Creating a ReactJS portfolio
- Learning React components, React Router, React Hooks, & React List Styling

Skills

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Dart

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Next.js, Vue.js, Laravel, Flutter, React Native, Node.js

Tools & Platforms

Git, Github, Vercell, Wordpress, Figma, Firebase, Visual Studio Code

Soft Skill

Design Thinking, Communication Skills, Teamwork, Time Management, Quality Awareness

Selected Projects

Learning App Aksun

Aksun is an innovative learning platform designed to make it easier for users to learn reading the Sundanese script. This app provides learning materials, allows users to take quizzes with three different difficulty levels, and view rankings based on quiz results. With Aksun, learning Sundanese script becomes more interactive and enjoyable.